[Music]
[Música]
The resources that I have to make
los recursos que tengo para hacer que
that debate real, I've used them
ese debate sea real yo los he utilizado
both with Dallas, he told me yes
tanto con Dallas me ha dicho que sí a
completely, you know, and Ricky is the one who right now,
tope sabes y y Ricky es el que ahora
well, no, he can't accept that
mismo Pues no no termina de aceptar que
between Dallas, between Dallas, we're going to split up,
entre Dallas que entre Dallas vamos a
man, from the simple fact that the
partir tío del simple hecho de que la
police don't tell you, you have to put a
policía no te dice tienes que poner de
restraining order, you request that from
alejamiento eso lo solicitas al juzgado
the court, the only thing you do is
en la policía lo único que haces es
file a complaint for
poner en todo caso una denuncia por
threats, which he hasn't done either
amenazas cosa que tampoco lo ha hecho
because he threatened me in the first
porque él me amenazó a mí en un primer
place, I mean, it's true, it's
lugar o sea es de verdad es que me pare
incredible to me that he understands it and by the way, what
increíble que lo entienda y por cierto
you said in your own
al tú dijiste tambén en tu propio
live show is that he hasn't filed that supposed complaint,
directo es que esa supuesta denuncia que
but if he had, he would
no ha puesto pero si la hubiese puesto
file it more than half a year later and he
la pone más de medio año después y justo
files it right when I read the first video
la pone cuando yo leedo el primer vídeo
that I dedicate to the clown and right when I
que le dedico al payaso y justo cuando
tell him for the first time that we're going to
le digo por primera vez que vamos a
debate, come on, it can't be
debatir es que vamos es que no puede ser
more of a lie and more ridiculous, all of this, it
más mentira y más ridículo todo esto es
impresses me that someone even has
que me impresiona que alguien siquiera
any kind of credibility, it's pathetic,
ningún tipo de credibilidad es patético
aggressive things, no, he literally
cosas agresivas no literalmente se
dedicated himself to saying that he wanted to leave me
dedicó a decir que me quería partir la
the face just for hearing my name is out there the tweet and he's a [ __ ] liar of [ __ ] it's not true that you deleted it a month later this is totally false In fact I don't even know if he has deleted it but if he has deleted it it was in the
pero si lo ha borrado ha sido en este
last year only to play the [ __ ]
último año únicamente para hacer la [__]
victim this note there in the car
víctima esta nota por ahí en el coche
is mixed up in the gossip
está metido en el salseo
listen to me Ah he just sent this to you
escúchame Ah esto te lo acaba de enviar
now Of course of course now Ah you think you
ahora Claro claro ahora Ah pensas que lo
had it there prepared well And
tenías ahí preparado pues Y esto no lo
I didn't know this I didn't know what I
sabía yo esto no lo sabía yo lo que le
told him I told him I told Dallas man
dije yo le dije yo le dije a Dallas tío
and and IT FEELS bad for me because sometimes I get
y y me SAE mal porque a veces recibo
hit and I say please let me do
golpes que digo por favor dejadme hacer
my job you good you [ __ ] great but but
mi trabajo tú bien tú de [__] madre pero
man Dallas it comes out bad for me because
pero tío Dallas a mí me sale mal porque
with Dallas I know that he says that
yo a Dallas yo sé que él dice que no
we're not friends okay but I consider that
somos amigos vale pero yo Considero que
with dasas I have a very good reaction
con dasas Tengo una muy buena reacción
okay But it's not your fault for what he
vale Pero tú no tienes culpa de de lo
says But but man dasas to me
que diga Pero pero ostras a mí dasas a
dasas I got a little upset like
mí dasas se me molestó un poquito rollo
Uncle it's that why didn't you push him
de Tío es que por qué no le has apretado
more And I say it's that  Not me again I do
más Y digo es que yo no yo de nuevo Yo
n't know all the stories or all the
no sé todas las historias ni todas las
things I don't know that he has
cosas Yo no sé que él le ha amenazado
allegedly threatened Dallas I was
presuntamente a Dallas yo esto lo
unaware of this then Of course if it
desconocía entonces Claro si realmente
's really true I told dasas Dalas There is
es cierto yo le dije a dasas Dalas Hay
some point that you didn't like you have
algún punto que no te ha gustado tienes
a place you are very much invited so that you
un lugar estás invitadísimo para que tú
give him the same treatment that I have given him because if I am something it is impartial
doy a ti porque si algo soy es Imparcial
now obviously if I have things
ahora bien Obviamente si yo hay cosas
that I don't know what I'm going to do to him, I mean I
que no sé qué le voy a hacer o sea yo
pressed with technicalities and things
apreté con tecnicismos y cosas
Dallas accepts it Yes but dasas dasas
el Dallas lo acepta Sí pero dasas dasas
would have to yes but when when Ricky
tendría que sí pero cuando cuando Ricky
proposes the debate And this is true
le propone el debate Y esto es cierto
because what I understand because
porque lo que tengo entendido porque
technically it is written by discord and
técnicamente está escrito por discord y
daras can check it discord
daras lo puede chequear discord
technically when Rick tells him I
técnicamente cuando Rick le dice Te
invite you to do a debate with me on
invito a hacer un debate conmigo en
elital which is his podcast Although now he
elital que es su podcast Aunque ahora lo
has it a little inactive dasas tells him that he is
tiene un poco inactivo dasas le dice que
going to rip off his arm or something like that I do
le va a arrancar un brazo o algo así Eso
not justify that no then
no lo justifico eso no entonces
obviously man if they are going to give you the debate
obviamente tío si te van a dar el debate
you tell him that you are going to rip off his
tú le dices que le vas a arrancar un
arm you can understand that  the other one says
brazo puedes entender que el otro dice
damn let's not have much debate
[__] poco debate vamos a hacer
then I think that if Dallas really
entonces yo creo que si Dallas de verdad
said look I want to have a
dijera e Mira quiero hacer un debate de
good debate pi arran I won't rip off any of your
buenas pi arran no te arranco ningún
arms and I won't rip off any limbs like it's
brazo y no arranco ninguna extremidad en
not fair to rip off limbs I
plan no se vale arrancar extremidades yo
think that we could get to do the dal
creo que se podría llegar a hacer el dal
el dala I think that what he
el dala yo creo que te lo que te lo
accepts you right now but Ricky No but
acepta ahora mismo pero el Ricky No pero
look at Ricky But if you say Okay
mira el Ricky Pero si tú dices Bueno
come on Okay then not in person in case they
venga Vale pues en persona no por si se
get aggressive Because also they are two
ponen agresivos Porque además son dos
people who have a lot of things to
personas que tienen muchas cosas que
throw at each other It's that I know them
echarse en cara Es que yo conozco a los
both and I think that just as they could
dos y creo que igual que se podrían
get along very well it could get along
llevar muy bien se podrí llevar eso se
I told Dallas a long time ago
lo decía yo al Dallas hace mucho tiempo
because I got along with Ricky or rather and
porque yo me llevaba con Ricky o sea y
I got along with Dallas and I got along
yo me llevaba con Dallas y me llevaba
with Ricky and I got along with both
con Ricky y me llevaba los dos
obviously not the same Deal with
evidentemente no el mismo Trato con los
both of them but I got along with Ricky l have you
dos pero me llevaba con Ricky l tú has
seen have you seen the island of
visto tú has visto la isla de las
temptations they put a glass in the
tentaciones que ponen un cristal en
middle of the beach so that they have I do
medio de la playa para que tengan hago
this I put a glass in the middle of the Setup
así pongo un cristal en medio del Setup
of the set and one side of the other so that
del plató y un lado del otro para que no
I don't have  taken uncle to me I have
yo me he llevado tío a mí yo me he
taken with rck here there have been nights
llevado con rck yo aquí he habido noches
until until recently when I have been
hasta hasta hace poco que me he puesto
with here ha by discord hant and I
con aquí ha por discord hant y yo no
had no problem with him some
tenía ningún problema con él alguna
slip he had made with me And such But
patinada había metido conmigo Y tal Pero
but he blocked me because I brought up the
pero él me bloqueó porque saqué lo de
Tudor thing and the Lali thing and it's like and now then after
tudor y lo de Lali y es como y ahora
time he came out proving us
luego al tiempo ha salido dándonos la
right to what we were saying
razón a lo que estábamos diciendo
that Lali was lying that I don't
nosotros que la Lali estaba mintiendo
know what no How much is it that this
que no sé qué no Cuánto es que este
guy has an attitude and an ego I don't
chico tiene una actitud y un ego yo no
know if it's age and with age it
sé si será la edad y con la edad
will change but these are things that are things that
cambiará pero son cosas que son cosas
no but Dallas would accept a
que no pero el Dallas aceptaría un
debate in person and live and this one wouldn't
debate en persona y en directo y este no
accept it even live because
te lo aceptaría ni en directo porquees
you say come on okay in person no because it's
tú dices venga vale en persona no porque
not going to be that the thing sa end
no vay a ser que la cosa sa acabe
Hot but if it is that Ricky I wouldn't
Caliente pero si es que el Ricky No te
accept it even live here
lo aceptaría ni ni por en directo aquí
Ricky wouldn't
el Ricky no te lo
accept it I'm going to give it a spin I'm going to
aceptaría voy a darle una vuelta voy a
give it a spin it makes me angry it makes me
dar una vuelta es que me da rabia Me da
angry it makes me angry because I don't
rab me da rabia me da rabia porque no
want to do a podcast eh eh By
quiero hacer un podcast eh eh Por
call because it seems like a piece to me  of
llamada porque me parece un pedazo de
crap because I like that seado we
truño porque me gusta que seado lo
do it here here they make crap we
hacemos aquí aquí se hacen truño lo
do it here you and I and Dallas and Ricky
hacemos aquí tú y yo y el Dallas y Ricky
you and I here moderating and and Dallas
tú y yo aquí moderando y y el Dallas te
accepts it the ri the Ricky No Ricky is
lo acepta el ri el Ricky No el Ricky te
going to tell you that the restraining order is
va a decir que la orden de alejamiento
not valid over the internet either that over the
tampoco vale por internet que por
internet they cannot be on the
internet tampoco se pueden estar en la
same call you yes I believe I tell you
misma llamada te sí cre te digo te digo
the truth eh I doubt very much that r that
la verdad eh dudo mucho que r que
accept to do a debate on your channel
aceptar hacer un un debate en tu canal
for an issue of not wanting you to
por un tema de que no quisiera que te
take the visits I know Ricky if you
lleves las visitas Yo sé que Ricky si
accept a collaboration with me here
aceptas un colaborado conmigo aquí
fighting the two of us and to collaborate with but
peleándonos los dos y a colabor con per
now I think now from what I
ahora creo ahora por lo que tengo
understand no it is not on good terms
entendido no no es tn buenos términos
because of the fact that he had you blocked or something
por lo de que te tenía bloqueado o algo
like that it also surprises me that I am going to
así igual me sorprende que me va hacer
miss it I am going to miss it the
falta me va a hacer falta a mí lo el
money that I am going to earn with a
dinero que vaya a ganar yo con un
live stream I am going to miss aes I think it
directo me va a hacer falta aes Yo creo
is an issue of ego maybe of not
que es un tema de de ego quizá de no
wanting this person to help her I
quiero a esta persona ayudarla yo te
tell you I can propose to him I can
digo yo le puedo proponer yo le puedo
tell him and would you do the debate by
decir e harías el debate por
video call I think he will
videollamada yo creo que ese sí lo
accept that one  eh yes he already told you no, I think he
acepta eh si ya te dijo que no creo yo
told you no, I think no, I have
que te dijo que no yo creo que no yo
never never proposed a
nunca le Nunca le he propuesto un
video call to him because I don't like him but if you are
videollamada porque no me gusta pero si
so insistent, I can
tanta insistencia tenéis yo le puedo
convey the message wait He
transmitir el mensaje espérate Me me
is telling me something true so that I
está diciendo algo verd para que lo
put it also that he wants to say something but
ponga también que quiere decir algo pero
that is ridiculous man when he knows
que es la ridiculez tío cuando él sabe
perfectly well that this order of is that it
perfectamente que esta orden de es que
sounds even ridiculous to say it an
suena hasta hasta ridículo decirlo una
order of no, no, I am not going to debate
orden de no no yo con dar no debato
because and he knows very well that this has not even been
porque y él sabe sobra que esto ni se la
accepted if it is true that he has
han aceptado si es verdad que la ha
put it or that he has requested it, nor is
puesto o que lo ha solicitado ni se pide
the police station requested nor have they accepted it in the
la comisaría ni se la han aceptado en el
case that he has made it, nor is he going to nor does he
caso que la haya hecho ni ni va ni le
get to give this complaint that he says he has
llega a dar a la denuncia esta que dice
put that it is not going to be arrived if you have been
que ha puesto que no se va a llegar si
laughing at these threats for a year It
llevas un año riéndote de esas amenazas
seems very bad to me what I told you and
Me parece muy mal delox clo que te dije
you in private now you are telling without
ya ti en privado ahora ests contando sin
asking my permission to any guy in
pedirme permiso a ningún tipo en el
Javier's live now I tell you eh And
directo de Javier ahora te lo digo eh Y
also presently what I told you, not even the reason
ademá esente lo que te dije ni la razón
why I told you totally
de Por qué te lo dije totalmente
different from what I told you  I recommend
distinto a lo que te dije te recomiendo
rereading it again and I don't like that
releerlo de nuevo y no me gusta que
you go around saying the things that I told
andes diciendo las cosas que te dije yo
you privately in confidence and Ah, you
a ti en privado en confianza y Ah lo
let it out in public, you're discussing what
sueltes en público está discutiendo lo
Rick had said, no, this at no
que había dicho Rick no esto en ningún
time anything about you nor was I
momento nada de sobre ti ni estaba
saying anything about
diciendo nada sobre
you It was Ricky who threatened me in
ti Fue Ricky el que me amenazó a mí en
the first place, then after that he
un primer lugar luego después de eso se
has dedicated himself to bringing up a lot of topics
ha dedicado a meterse un montón de temas
that I didn't even know about you in my videos
que ni conocía que los ti en mis vídeos
the son of a [ __ ] saying nonsense that
el hijo de perra diciendo barbaridades
eh when people suspected that
de que eh cuando la gente sospechaba que
I had broken up with liis and he started doing a
yo había roto con liis y se puse hac un
lot of [ __ ] [ __ ] too and I have never
montón de [__] [__] también e Yo en
said at any time that I was going to
ningún momento he dicho que le fua
rip off his arm in the debate and I have always
arrancar un brazo en el debate y siempre
said that we did it without any kind
he dicho que lo hacíamos sin ningún tipo
of problem with people there and if he
de problema con gente ahí y si que
takes people because he is afraid of me, I don't care it's that I'm
llevar la gente porque me tiene miedo me
not going to attack him in the
da igual es que no le voy a agredir en
middle of the [ __ ] debate, I simply want to
medio del [__] debate simplemente quer
make him look bad talking because I don't need to
dejarlo mal hablando porque no necesito
resort to violence to make him look bad,
recurrir a la violencia para dejarlo mal
that simple and That's all so
así de sencillo e Eso es todo entonces
if he doesn't want to it's only because he's
si él no quiere es únicamente porque es
a coward and because he knows it looks bad and that's it There's
un [__] y porque sabe que queda mal y
no more turning back or  be that it does
punto No hay más vuelta de hoja o sea
not go with nonsense and
que no vaya con tonterías de y
victimhood of Oh, dasas is crazy
victimismo de Ay es que dasas está loco
because the only one who is out of his [ __ ]
porque el único que está mal de la [__]
mind is the one who was sleeping with me since
cabeza es el que iba acostándome desde
2016, buddy, no, no, 2015, I think I do not
2016 colega no no 2015 creo no me
remember very well, in the end I got the
acuerdo muy bien al final me levo la
host eh, the police do not tell you you have to
[__] eh la policía no te dice tienes
put a restraining order, it is
que poner una orden de alejamiento es
that they do not even offer you that, that
que ni siquiera te ofrecen esa ese ese
matter in Yes, that is requested later in
asunto en Sí eso se solicita después
court, the police will take your complaint in any case
juzgado la policía te toma en todo caso
for threats and then they will
la denuncia por amenazas y luego ya te
divert you to the court. Poras the evidence
desviarán al juzgado A poras las pruebas
that the police but you do not put a
que se la policía pero no pones un orden
restraining order with the police nor do they tell you
de alejamiento en la policía ni te dicen
absolutely anything in any advice of anything It is
absolutamente nada en ningún consejo de
stupid man, it is really
nada Es que es estúpido tío verdad es
ridiculous, you have not said anything, you have not
que ridículo no has contado nada no has
told me, let's see, me, Dallas, if
contado a ver yo yo Dallas si te ha
something has bothered you, I apologize
molestado algo te pido disculpas
publicly. No, I do not think I have said anything, I do
públicas No yo no creo que he dicho nada
not think I have said anything wrong, eh, but
no creo que haya dicho nada mal eh pero
I can understand that, well, what do I know, it is not the
yo puedo entender que pues yo que sé no
same as what I said before about
s igual que lo que he dicho antes de
Auron, that sometimes I say things that I think
auron que yo a veces digo cosas que creo
are not bad and maybe I go
que no son malas y a lo mejor me
too far, ma  my bad eh And regarding and
extralimitó ma mala mía eh Y respecto y
regarding what about Ricky, let's
respecto a lo de respecto a lo de Ricky
see technically Ricky says it in the
a ver técnicamente Ricky lo dice en el
podcast I see that there
podcast veo que no hay necesidad de
's no need to lie there technically he invites him to the podcast that we have seen in the extract and daras tells him that if he goes and has him in person I don't know if it's ripping off an arm or I'll give it to you I don't know I put it in the Ricky says it in
Lo ponía en el lo dice Ricky en el de
this I mean maybe I'm confused with this
esto O sea a lo mejor me confundo con el
tweet where he told kku that
tweet este que le dijo a kku lo de que
a leg is going to fly off or
le va a salir una una pierna volando o
something like that but without more than I
algo así pero que sin más que yo
understand that adaras's ways sometimes
entiendo que las formas adaras a veces
fail him when he has those types of
le fallan cuando tiene esa ese tipo de
opportunities and then obviously
oportunidades y luego obviamente la
people shield themselves In that I defended him that you have
gente se escuda En eso yo lo defendí que
n't put that eh dasas there you haven't
eso no lo has puesto eh dasas ahí no me
told me anything eh [ __ ] but when
has dicho nada eh cabrón pero cuando
Ricky says that I say I
Ricky dice eso yo le digo yo a Dalas lo
know Dalas and I think that no
conozco y creo que no no pasaría
absolutely nothing would happen and I say because I
absolutamente nada y digo porque yo
knew adalas off camera and then
conoci adalas fuera de cámaras y luego
in the videos and in the videos he does a lot of
en los vídeos y en los vídeos hace mucho
show business and I can understand that
show business y puedo entender que a
sometimes he does  comments that he leaves I
veces hace comentarios que se le va Yo
take them as humor Honestly,
me los tomo como humor Honestamente a mí
if one day Tas writes to me upset And
si un día Tas me escribe molesto Y me
says I'm going to rip your leg off, I
dice te voy a arrancar una pierna yo me
laugh. I mean, the truth is, I'm leaving, I don't
río O sea la verdad yo me vo yo no me
laugh, I mean, I
río o sea yo los mensajes estos que le
don't justify these messages that he sent to Ricky and it does
mandó al Ricky yo eso no lo justifico y
n't make sense. No, I don't know the context of
no tiene sentido no no sé el contexto de
the conversation that they were in at that
la conversación que estaban en ese
moment but I don't put that. I don't
momento pero yo no pongo eso yo yo no
have to see anything else, it's when they get
tengo a ver otra cosa ya es cuando
bigger but the one about I'm going to
cuando van a mayores pero el de te voy a
rip your arm off, I can't take it
arrancar un brazo yo no puedo tomármelo
in any other way than humor because I
de otra manera que no sea humor porque
say that nobody says it seriously okay
digo que nadie lo dice en serio vale
something else, it's when he talks about
otra cosa ya es cuando habla de de
hitmen or things like that, what
sicarios o cosas de este estilo lo que
happened with Millo, I understand that there pu pu a
pasó con el millo entiendo que ahí pu pu
Well, I can see that a
un Pues yo eso sí que lo puedo ver un
little more, like, jeez, I don't know but well, that
poco más así de ostras no sé pero bueno
's it, no I mean, man Because you see it as more
es eso no O sea hombre Porque ve veo más
plausible that you send a third party to scare you,
plausible que envíes a un tercero a
for God's sake, than
pegarte un susto por Dios que no a que
you ripping someone's leg off, you
tú le arranques una pierna a alguien
know, no, no, but no,
sabes no no pero no
buo, I was friends with delox, I was friends with
buo yo era amigo de delox yo era amigo
delox until  I was friends with Delos
de delox hasta que yo era amigo de delos
until I wasn't but the point is that let's
hasta que no pero es que el punto es que
see, I understand Well look now
a ver es que entiendo Pues mira ahora
just like he told you no Javi
igual que él te dijo no el Javi
takes the opportunity to talk to you about me
aprovecha para hablar contigo de mí
because I have him blocked I talk about
porque yo lo tengo bloqueado yo hablo de
Ricky about Whoever wants whoever has me
Ricky de Qui quiera el que me tenga
blocked Javi Javi Honestly I
bloqueado Javi Javi Honestamente yo
'm fed up with this subject I'm
estoy hasta el Nao de este tema yo te
going to be clear with you if you want I
voy a ser claro yo si queréis le
propose to do a debate by
propongo hacer un debate por
video call which I think is something that
videollamada que creo que es algo que no
shouldn't be a problem okay And I
debería suponer un problema vale Y eso
put that and I say Ricky Look they're
lo pongo y le digo Ricky Mira me están
bothering me with the [ __ ] debate do
dando la brasa con el [__] debate
you want to do a debate by video call
quieres hacer un debate por videollamada
And if he accepts that I accept and I know I
Y si acepta que acepte y yo se yo se lo
can tell him I know that now he's traveling to
puedo decir sé que ahora está de viaje a
a magic event that's why he didn't
una a un evento de magia que por eso no
go to the eslan but when he comes back I'll be
fue a los eslan pero cuando vuelva yo se
happy to tell him I say Look Hey This
lo digo encantado le digo Mira Eh Esto
is what there is and let's see if he wants to I'll
es lo que hay y a ver si quiere ya te
tell you I'm the first one that would
digo yo soy el primero que que me
love for a debate to be held eh and I'll
encantaría que se hiciera un debate eh e
even tell you if one day it happens I'll
incluso te digo si algún día se hace yo
let you come as a moderator let him say or we
te dejo venir de moderador deja decir o
do it here on your channel if he accepts
lo hacemos aquí en tu canal si acepta
For me there is no  problem but [ __ ]
Por mí no hay problema pero hostias
eh the dasas is watching us dasas eh would
eh el el dasas nos está viendo dasas eh
you accept a debate Yes I think he
tú aceptarías un debate Sí yo creo que
accepts it by video call and in person
lo acepta por vide llamada y en persona
I think so and by phone if
yo creo que sí y por teléfono si hace
necessary What happens is that Ricky No but
falta Lo que pasa que el Ricky No pero
well the point yeah let's see if the point is
bueno el punto si a ver si el punto es
basically that the guy is using
básicamente que el tío está utilizando
some [ __ ] to say no I can't, I
una chorrada de decir no yo no puedo o
mean you spend 5 years
sea te pegas 5 años
challenging me now that you're making a
retándome ahora que estás haciendo el
fool of yourself with the teaser And with all this
ridículo con el teaser Y con toda la
nonsense No now it's not that I have
tontería esta No ahora no es que lo he
reported him, I mean after everything that
denunciado o sea después de todo lo que
has been said about him it's not that I have
ha dicho de él no es que lo he
reported him and I have a
denunciado y tengo una orden de
restraining order and it's like dude or rather more
alejamiento y es como tío o sea más
ridiculous it can't be done but I am
ridículo no se puede hacer pero yo estoy
completely in agreement with you that
Completamente de acuerdo contigo en que
this issue must be closed with a debate
este tema hay que cerrarlo con un debate
okay let's see a debate is done on the channel
vale a ver un debate se hace en el canal
that they want if they want to do it
que ellos quieran si lo quieren hacer
here of course of course I'm not going to
aquí por supuesto claro Yo no lo voy a
say no obviously and then
decir que no evidentemente y y luego
they are going to upload it to their
ellos lo van a subir a sus canales
edited channels and all that stuff like they
editados y todo el rollo ese como
always do and so on okay we just
siempre hacen y demás vale nosotros nos
get into nothing But if I
metemos ha nada simplemente Pero si yo
look I'll tell you more I'll tell you  more I don't
mira yo te digo más te digo más yo no
even need to be in the debate I don't give a
hace falta ni que esté en el debate a mí
damn there are people who say it's not
me la chupa que hay gente que dice no es
that he wants to take me look at them
que delo se quiere llevar a mí mira que
doing it with Javi with Dallas and Ricky so it
lo hagan con Javi con Dallas y Ricky así
splashes me even less you leave me alone
me salpica aún menos a mí me dejáis
if I don't give a damn I do the
tranquilos si a mí me la pela yo hago el
podcast for the love of art the last thing I
podcast por amor al arte lo último que
want is to have problems well he
quiero es es tener problemas yo pues me
sent me an audio of TR minutes I
ha mandado un audio de TR minutos yo
go in here d go in here go
entra aquí d entra aquí entra
directly It's that I think he's out
directamente Es que creo que está fuera
come on I put this audio and we move on to the
venga pongo este audio y pasamos al
next topic because the next topic You
siguiente tema que el siguiente tema Ya
see what's going to fall on me now d
ves la que me va a caer ahora d por
please have mercy Look I didn't want to start
favor ten piedad Mira no quería estarme
saying this because really
poniendo a decir esto porque de verdad
eh de nuo I'm going to repeat myself The only thing I
eh de nuo vol a repetir Lo único que
wanted was eh to deny the subject this
quería era eh desmentir el tema este
idiot and the lies because Ricky is a
estúpido y las mentiras porque es un
[ __ ] mythomaniac I mean he's a
puñetero mitómano el Ricky o sea es
compulsive liar and that's the only thing I
mentiroso compulsivo y es lo único de lo
was talking about but deox you
que estaba hablando pero es que deox te
started saying something that isn't true it
has puesto a decir algo que no es así no
's not true I mean I don't care
es así cierto o sea a mí no me importa
that a person with whom I have no
que una persona a la que no tengo ningún
contact whatsoever I have no contact whatsoever
tipo de contacto no tengo ningún tipo de
neither comings nor goings of any kind,
ni de idas ni venidas de ningún tipo
take and interview whoever it is that I do not care
coja y entrevista a quien sea es que me
But what I told you and eh is
da igual Pero lo que yo te dije y eh es
what bothers me Precisely what you have
lo que me molesta Precisamente lo que
said and I do not understand either Javi, no, I do not
has dicho y no entiendo tampoco Javi no
see it as bad first of all that Sao
lo no lo vea mal primero todo que Sao
that I told you in confidence in private
que te dije a ti en confianza en privado
no So that you go and tell it in
no Para que cojas y lo cuentas en el
Javi's live that I have been upset
directo de Javi de que me he molestado
with you but it's that yes Besides you are going to
contigo pero es que si Además vas a
tell it eh keep in mind that on top of that it
contarlo eh ten en cuenta que encima no
is not as you are saying I told you that I have been
es como estás diciendo Yo te dije que me
upset because the relationship
había molestado porque la relación
with you over time has ended up
contigo con el tiempo ha terminado
being more and more one of trust and
siendo cada vez más de confianza y yo
for you I would I mean I would do bigger things for you
por ti haría O sea yo por ti haría cosas
and in fact I have already fought
más grandes y de hecho ya me he peleado
for you with things eh that people are
por ti con cosas eh que la gente te est
accusing you and that they are accusing
acusando a ti y que me estén acusando a
me and you are not capable of standing up for
mí y tú no seas capaz de dar la cara por
me as I have also stood up for you in
mí como yo también la he dado por ti en
other moments having had in these
otros momentos habiendo tenido en estos
last these last weeks more
últimos estas últimas semanas más
contact and more friendship for me that is
contacto y más amistad para mí eso es
something that I did not give a friend because
algo que yo no le di un amigo porque yo
for a friend I will fight my face with whoever it takes for
por un amigo me parto la cara con quien
a moment a moment  It's that they
haga falta un momento un momento es que
are three minutes I'm going to comment on one
son tres minutos Voy a comentado una
thing Only that I understand that it is that you do
cosa Solo que yo entiendo que es que tú
not have the same let's see how I do not
no tienes el mismo a ver como yo no
have the same context as Cos I let's
tienes tú el mismo contexto de Cos yo yo
see I'll tell you one thing first
a ver yo te digo una cosa lo primero
although I know that here the octopus is falling on me I
aunque yo sé que aquí me está cayendo el
take it as something nice because he
pulpo me lo tomo como algo bonito porque
is considering me a friend which stops
me está considerando amigo lo cual para
if he has told you something in private
a si te ha contado una cosa en privado
[ __ ] it is that of course but let's see what he told
cabrón es que claro pero a ver que lo
me in private
que me contó en privado ya lo ha dicho
he has already said it he has already said it eh So Dalas I
él ya lo ha dicho él eh Así que Dalas me
take it since you have said it you can
tomo la ya que lo has dicho tú puedo
comment I hope okay not me that it does not
comentar espero vale no me que no me
fall on me more more funa please yes but the thing about
caiga más más funa por favor sí pero lo
the defense with the subject
de lo de la defensa con el tema
simply simply of course
simplemente simplemente claro
simply He gets upset by what is
simplemente Él se molesta por lo que
said here because of the context that I may have
dice aquí por el contexto que yo puedo
left out and because of the fact
haberme dejado fuera e por el hecho de
that I have not shown my face maybe or I have not it is that
que yo no he dado la cara quizá o no he
I lack arguments man that's what I
es que me faltan argumentos tío es lo
tell you I do not know everything so
que te digo yo no me lo sé todo entonces
what I do in a podcast is understand
yo lo que hago en un podcast es entender
that what they tell me is true s but
que lo que me dicen es verdad s pero de
anyway anyway if you
todas manera de todas maneras si tú te
get along with both of them neither  you're going to
llevas bien con los dos tampoco te vas a
start fighting with one or the other and
poner a pelearte con uno o con el otro y
for example what I do is I tell him I tell
yo por ejemplo lo que hago es le digo le
Ricky I told Ricky Ricky I
digo a Ricky yo le dije a Ricky Ricky yo
think you've gone too far you've both gone too far
creo que te has pasado de la raya ambos
and he says Ricky and then his
os habéis pasado y me dice Ricky ahí le
face changes no if you notice I've
cambia la cara no si te das cuenta te lo
told you before he says both of us we've
he dicho antes te dice los dos los dos
gone too far and that's when I got angry
nos hemos pasado y ahí yo me puse negro
because I say No no you more than Dallas
porque digo No no tú más que el Dallas
still or D has told you about the arm
todavía oa el D te ha dicho lo del brazo
but it's that you said it ma I
pero es que tú lo has dicho má yo le
told him I told him man I do think you've
dije yo le dije hombre Yo sí que creo
gone too far and I explained to him
que te has pasado y le expliqué el Por
Why did I think there are more things
qué creía que ahora hay más cosas de
again I insist on starting a [ __ ] debate it's
nuevo insisto hacepto un [__] debate es
that I'm not prepared with buah I'm going to
que yo no voy preparado con buah voy a
get all this artillery of evidence
pillar toda esta artillería de pruebas
I don't know it but apart from that
Yo lo descon no pero aparte aparte que
you don't have it so present and you're not
tú no lo tienes tan presente y no estás
as involved as I am Of course I feel
tan metido como yo Claro a mí me sabe
bad for me That's why For example I can
mal Yo por eso Por ejemplo yo puedo
understand when for example
entender cuando por ejemplo me vino aquí
Silvia Charro came here came here to put
me vino aquí Silvia Charro a meter
[ __ ] on your channel I didn't take it badly
[__] en tu canal yo no me lo tomé mal
that you were there because I say  wow,
que tú estuvieras ahí porque yo digo bua
Javi is missing this argument and the
es que Javi le falta este argumento y lo
other thing. Because they are complex issues, he won't
otro Porque son temas complejos no lo
know. I simply said, Okay, he's
sabrá yo simplemente dije Okay está
doing his job, he's covering a
haciendo su trabajo está cubriendo una
news story, whatever, okay. It's okay. I
noticia lo que sea okay No pasa nada yo
told him, give me some space so we can
le dije Me das un espacio para poder
debate. I came from Bat and that's it. I left so
debatir vine de batí y ya está y me fui
happy. I'll give you the same
tan contento yo a daras le doy el mismo
space. So I think that's what
espacio Entonces yo creo que ahí es lo
I can do. ig, let's see the topic, it
que yo puedo hacer ig a ver el tema no
's not that. Let's see, the topic is also here.
es ese a ver el tema es aquí igual sube
People who don't get along with Dallas come up. I
gente que se lleva mal con el Dallas yo
can't. I don't get along with all the
no me puedo yo no me llevo mal con toda
people who don't get along in Dallas. There are
la gente que se lleva mal Dallas yo hay
many people that he doesn't get along with that I do. I'm
mucha gente con la que él no se lleva
not going to be
que yo sí me llevo no me voy a estar
fighting, you know, but man. The thing is that it
peleando sabes pero hombre Lo que pasa
's true that I'm not
es que sí que es verdad que tú no te lo
going to tell you any other way. I'm going to
voy a decir de otra manera yo te lo voy
tell you any other way. If I
a decir de otra manera si yo llego a
had the correct context, I'd be the
tener el contexto correcto soy el
first to throw it at him because I have
primero que se lo tira porque no tengo
no problem. I have confidence
ningún problema Yo tengo confianza tanto
in both Ricky and Dallas. Now,
con Ricky como con Dallas ahora bien
things that I don't know, I feel bad about myself. I
cosas que no sé me sabe mal yo yo
understand that Dallas, man, is that the bastard
entiendo que Dallas tío es que el cabrón
is a newspaper archive.  the guy knows everything
es una hemeroteca se lo sabe todo el tío
So of course the guy suddenly tells me
Entonces claro el tío de repente me dice
No, it's that here this and that so
No es que aquí esto y lo otro para que
you get an idea, I don't I thought that
te hagas una idea yo no Yo pensaba que
these threats so to speak that
estas amenazas entre comillas que le
come to Ricky for which he then puts or
llegan a Ricky por las que luego pone o
requests the [ __ ] restraining order,
solicita la [__] orden de alejamiento
this is so crazy that I'm fed
esta de las narices que ya estoy hasta
up with it, I thought they were
el Nao de ella pensaba que eran
recent, not from I don't know how long ago, so you
recientes no de hace no sé cuánto tiempo
see, I mean, in my
para que veas es decir entonces en mi
head, well, the guy had an
cabeza es bueno el tío ha tenido una
argument, he received some threats
discusión le han llegado o unas amenazas
or whatever because of what I
o lo que sea a raíz de que lo que le
said to him and what I threw in Ricky's face,
dije yo y lo que le eché en cara a Ricky
dude, it can't be that you're
es tío no puede ser que tú estés
saying that you're going to sue Dallas or
diciendo que vas a denunciar a Dallas o
that Lali is going to sue Dallas and you're not
que Lali va a denunciar a Dallas y no
suing the guy who supposedly
denuncias al que se supone que ha
raped Lali, I mean, What the [ __ ] That
violado a a Lali o sea What the fuck Eso
seems crazy to me And I threw that
me parece una locura Y eso se lo heche
in her because that's something that I do know so of course I
en cara porque eso es algo que yo sí sé
There I tell you if I'm
entonces claro yo Ahí ya te digo si me
missing context, I can't do more
falta contexto no puedo hacer más de
again, what I can do is put the
nuevo yo lo que puedo es poner los
same resources at, let's say, the
mismos recursos a a digamos a
disposal of Dallas and Dallas I'm telling you
disposición de Dallas y Dallas te digo
Although now  in the minute and a half that's
Aunque ahora en el minuto y medio que
left of the audio, don't give me an
quede de audio me vuelvas a meter una
educational slap again. I'm glad you
colleja educativa me alegra que me
appreciate me and I'm taking it as something
tengas aprecio y me lo llevo como algo
positive. I'm going to try Vero, yes, there I will
positivo voy a tratar de Vero sí ahí sí
tell you yes. Let's see, of course, yes, yes, yes, yes, it's what you
te digo que sí a ver claro ya si si si
're talking about. Yes, he
es eso que estáis comentando me si te la
told you in private. I thought it was
ha dicho en privado Yo es que me creía
known in public. I'm telling you. You
que se sabía en público yo yo te digo yo
know what happens, look, I read it
Es que sabes qué pasa mira lo he leído
before in the chat that someone said,
antes en el chat que decía una una
someone said, the same thing happens to me as
persona decía a mí me pasa igual que a
you delox, I don't know how to keep secrets because I do
ti delox no sé guardar secretos porque
n't know what secrets are. Of course, I did
no sé que son secretos claro es que yo
n't know that it was something like super
no sabía que eso era algo como super
delicate. No, no, I haven't given it any
delicado no no yo no le he dado
importance. But well, in my head, it's
importancia Pero bueno en mi cabeza es
good that he may have been a little upset.
bueno se se ha podido molestar un poco
Well, I mean, I haven't given it a
Bueno pues o sea tampoco le daado una
huge importance. Let's listen and
importancia brutal vamos a escuchar y
that you haven't been able to do it.
que tú no hayas sido capaz de hacerlo
That's what has bothered me
Eso es lo que me ha molestado
personally. If you and I had
personalmente si tú y yo tuviésemos
purely professional contact, I would do
contacto meramente profesional me haría
totally the same. But at the moment when we are
totalmente igual pero momento en el que
going to do or consider ourselves something
ya vamos a hacer o considerarnos algo
more, That's where it bothers me and it has
más Ahí es donde me molesta y me ha
bothered me twice as much that you on top of that take it and
molestado el doble que encima cojas y me
make me look like  if I were a [ __ ]
hagas quedar como si fuera un [__]
angry person or a jealous piece of [ __ ] or not knowing
ardido o un celoso de [__] o no saber
what the [ __ ] because people talk and say
qué [__] porque la gente habl y dice
whatever they want when that wasn't
lo que le da la gana cuando esa no fue
the conversation that wasn't what I
la conversación así no fue lo que te
told you to me it doesn't bother me that you do your
dije a mí no me molesta que tú hagas tu
job but it's that when we [ __ ] and
trabajo pero es que ya cuando cogemos y
mix because it's not
mezclamos porque ya no es que sea
just work It's that on top of that you and
simplemente trabajo Es que encima tú y
I have been meeting after this
yo hemos estado quedando después de esto
last few weeks even more and
de esta última semanas más todavía y
talking more and playing and I don't know what and I don't
hablando más y jugando y no sé qué y no
know how many for me the relationship stops
sé cuántos para mí la relación deja de
being work-related or just that of a
ser laboral o sipre emente de un
coworker to become something more and
compañero de trabajo para ha algo más y
that I am capable of beating
que yo me sea capaz de partir la cara
you up or whatever Sorry with you not for you
contigo o sea Perdón contigo no por ti
because people are accusing you of [ __ ]
porque la gente estoy acusando de [__]
And you when this clown who
Y tú cuando este payaso que literalmente
is literally lying word after word is
está mintiendo una palabra tras está
lying and you know it I haven't been able
mintiendo y tú lo sabes no he sido capaz
to [ __ ] him and say four things it's like well
de [__] y decirle cuatro cosas es como
then we are not on the same level
pues entonces no estamos a mismo nivel
of friendship and that is what I
de amistad y eso es a lo que yo me
was referring to basically I stand up
estaba refiriendo básicamente Yo me paro
for you
la cara por ti
y L and that seems wrong to me what you did I already
yú L y eso me parece mal lo que hiciste
told you and it seems even worse to me
ya te lo dije y me parece peor todavía
that you said it  Now here live you have
que lo hayas dicho Ahora aquí en directo
n't asked my permission son and you
no me hayas pedido permis hio y le has
told him in a way that is not what I
contado de una manera que no es lo que
told you because what I told you is what I
te dije porque lo que te dije es lo que
'm telling you right now and I don't
te estoy diciendo ahora mismo y no
want to give many more details Because they
quiero dar muchos más detalles Porque
are part of private life but it's that you
son parte de la vida privada pero es que
force me to say it because it's that I'm going to be
me obligas a decirlo porque es que voy a
here now and again as if I
quedar aquí ahora y otra vez como si
were the [ __ ] idiot and it's not like that
fuera el [__] [__] y no es así
at all but there's more eh There's more And I
para nada pero hay más eh Hay más Y de
really don't understand Javi that you don't
verdad que no entiendo Javi que no lo
see it badly or I mean man you tell the things
veas mal o sea tío tú cuentas las cosas
that I tell you or even the times
que yo te digo a ti o incluso las veces
that maybe we've gotten angry about
que a lo mejor nos hemos mosqueado por
whatever and you go and And you say Ah well the
lo que sea y coges y Y dices Ah pues el
das told me that I don't know what no [ __ ] they
das me ha dicho que no sé qué no [__]
are private things and this about delo is also
son cosas privadas y esto de delo tamb
something private, it's not something that I should be
algo privado no es para que lo esté
telling here and publicly and also
contando aquí Y públicamente que además
that it has nothing to do eh Look at delox
que no tiene nada que ver eh Mira delox
Javi you will see that with the previous audio
Javi la verás que con el audio anterior
I got really confused my point is very
me he liado un montón mi punto es muy
simple m For a friend I will
sencillo m Yo por un amigo me parto la
fight with whoever it takes and that's it and to me
cara con quien haga falta y punto y a mí
The only thing that hurt me about that  is that I
Lo único que me dolió de eso es que yo
was considering delux a friend and
estaba considerando a delux un amigo y
with this act of Ricky well it hurt me
con este acto de Ricky pues me dolió
Because for me that doesn't make him a friend and
Porque para mí eso no lo hace un amigo y
I would not have taken that behavior
yo no hubiese tomado ese comportamiento
and that's it that is the only context
y ya está ese ese es el único contexto
of that is a private context that has nothing to
de eso es un contexto privado que nada
do with the public that is in
tiene que ver con lo público que va en
reference to my relationship with delux Ada
referencia a mi relación con delux Ada
that I have shat on people who are
que yo me he cagado en gente que le está
calling him a scammer publicly and and
llamando estafador públicamente y y
then seeing that he is not reciprocal that is what
luego ver que el no es recíproco eso es
has hurt me privately and
lo que a mí me ha dolido por privado y
this was not something to tell
esto no era algo para contar
publicly and it was not something that you
públicamente y no era algo que tú
had to take and say publicly
tuvieras que [__] y decir públicamente
at any time and period and now that
en ningún momento y punto y ahora que la
people are saying Oh Why is Dallas
gente esté diciendo Oh Porque Dallas es
a crybaby because Dallas gets angry because I do
un llorón porque Dallas se enfada porque
n't know what Because dasas tries to manipulate
no sé qué Porque dasas intenta manipular
for nothing but if I start to consider
para nada pero yo si empiezo a consir a
someone who is a friend and I start to
alguien que es una amig y empiezo a
have affection for someone who is not
tener cariño por alguien que no sea
capable of doing the same for me that I
capaz de hacer lo mismo por mí que yo
do for that person it hurts me and that's it okay
hago por esa persona me duele y eso es
want do you want to answer him
todo vale quiere quieres tú contestarle
before I if you want I give you my opinion
antes de yo si quieres te doy mi opinión
I want to give him a hug  to Dallas
Yo yo le quiero dar un abrazo a Dallas
eh Let's see me per come up before before
eh A ver a mí per sube antes antes de
the night is over come up and have a good time
que acabe la noche sube y ya se la pase
man it seems to me it seems endearing and
hombre me parece me parece entrañable y
I swear I feel bad because you know
te lo juro que me sabe mal porque sabes
how typical you put your foot in it without meaning to
lo típico que metes la pata sin querer
put your foot in it it's like in my head I
meter la pata se es como en mi cabeza yo
said it because it was something that in the
lo he dicho porque era algo que en
first place I saw it super innocent And
primer lugar lo veía super inocente Y en
secondly the one who looked bad was me I
segundo lugar quien quedaba mal era yo o
mean in any case I look bad because I
sea en todo caso quedo yo mal porque me
got in trouble you know or not So it's
ha caído bronca sabes o no Entonces es
like Well nothing happens at the end
como Bueno pues no pasa nada yo al final
of the day no I don't see anything wrong with it and that's it
del día no no le veo nada malo y ya está
In fact with me with dasas I thought that
De hecho yo con yo con dasas pensaba que
the issue was settled because I
ese tema estaba arreglado porque yo le
sent him some audios and everything on my part I
mandé unos audios y todo por mi parte lo
took it for
daba por
granted that we were talking about something about
zanjador que tenemos hablando una cosa
the island of temptations
de la isla de las tentaciones me
Lizy responded to me superb and I thought that
respondió lizy superb y yo pensaba que
everything was fine you know I'm telling you And the thing
estaba todo bien sabes ya te digo Y lo
about them calling him Yoron or something
de que le llamen yoron o algo
manipulative seems like a
manipulador me parece vamos una una
shame to me I haven't seen it on the chat
vergüenza yo no lo he visto por el chat
No but I would have told you
No pero yo te lo yo te lo hubiera dicho
privately because it's true that
por privado porque sí que es verdad que
now people are going to say  nonsense and such
ahora la gente va a decir tontería y tal
And in the end it is not that
Y al final tampoco tiene tanta
important and and and it will be given more
importancia y y y se le va dar más
importance than it has yes it is
importancia de la que tiene sí que es
true that he made that comment to you I
verdad que te ha dicho ese comentario Yo
am that when you said it I say what have you
es que cuando tú lo has dicho digo qué
said you have not said anything that
has dicho no has dicho nada ese
comment that you have told I did not
comentario que tú has contado yo no
know that he had made it to you
sabía que él te lo había hecho por
privately I believed that this was known
privado yo me creía que esto se sabía
but oh well what does it matter If
pero bueno qué más da Si de todas
anyway yes anyway Ricky has
maneras si de todas maneras el Ricky ha
told his part, I mean okay For my
contado su parte o sea vale Yo yo por mi
part I already tell you I think I understand his
parte ya te digo yo creo que entiendo su
point of saying no it's that of course
punto de que diga no es que claro yo
now but again if I don't have
ahora pero de nuevo si yo no tengo
tools I don't have context in my
herramientas no tengo contexto yo en mi
head I made a fair defense in my
cabeza hice una defensa justa en mi
head so I feel bad because
cabeza entonces me sabe mal porque
obviously maybe it could have been done
obviamente quizás se podía haber hecho
better in fact when I finished the the
mejor de hecho yo cuando terminé el el
podcast and all this I told him look
el podcast y todo esto yo le dije mira
record swear I could swear that I had told him
grab jurar juraría que yo le había dicho
that I was going to record with him and everything let's go I
que iba a grabar con él y todo lo vamos
have it out there what is certain and And
lo tengo por ahí lo que sí s seguro y Y
that as it is not anything personal that
eso como no es nada personal que me haya
he told me but what I have said I
dicho él sino que lo he dicho yo lo
can say is that I invited him to
puedo decir es que yo lo invité a él a
do a podcast because I found it
hacer un podcast porque me parecía
interesting that  after Ricky came to
interesante que luego de Ricky viniera a
him in case there was anything that Ricky
él por si había cualquier cosa que Ricky
had said that he didn't like, give him the
hubiera dicho que no le gustase darle el
same space and give it to him right in the
mismo espacio y dárselo justo el podcast
next podcast, you know. So for my part,
siguiente sabes Entonces yo por mi parte
the predisposition has always been
la predisposición siempre ha sido
positive and with the encouragement that we're going to let
positiva y con Ánimo de que vamos que
everyone give their point of view. The fact that
cada qui pueda dar su punto el hecho de
you bring people into your podcast is
que tú en tu podcast lleves a gente es
that I'm going to tell you the same thing that I
que te vuelvo a decir lo mismo que te he
told you before, I mean, I understand that he
dicho antes o sea yo entiendo que le le
may like it more or less that people that
podrá gustar más o menos que gente que
he considers friends or that he has a
que él considera amigo o que tiene una
friendship with get along with people that he doesn't,
amistad se lleve con gente que él no
but I imagine that he will understand. I'll
pero yo me imagino que él entenderá te
give you an example if Ivai tells me
pongo un ejemplo si a mí me dice ivai
tomorrow that he's coming here, I'll bring him, I mean,
mañana que viene aquí yo lo traigo o sea
an Ivai, man, I'm not going to bring you Coscu
un ivai hombre no te voy a traer a coscu
or I'm not going to bring you certain people
o no te voy a traer a ciertas personas
who have called him a pedophile, who have
que le han dicho pedófilo que le han
said other things to him, or I can bring him
dicho otras cosas o o lo puedo traer
to refute Tirso, okay, but man, I
para rebat Tirso vale pero hombre Yo
understand that this is as far as he goes, what
entiendo que hasta ahí Él llega a él lo
I see is that he's bothered okay is that
que yo veo que le ha molestado vale es
you haven't been able to refute
que tú no hayas sido capaz de rebatir le
Ricky. A lo  better with as much
al Ricky A lo mejor con con tanta
intensity as but let's see there
intensidad como pero a ver yo ahí lo que
what I understand is that you don't have eh You
lo que entiendo es que tú no tienes eh
're not so into the parrot and as
No estás tan metido en el loro y tan
put as maybe but that's what you
puesto como a lo mejor lo pero es lo que
have to understand that as subtle there is no
tiene que entender que como sutilo no
one no but outside of [ __ ] two things
hay nadie no pero fuera de coñ dos cosas
the first I lack context and the
la primera me falta contexto y la
second if I had it I would do it but with
segunda si lo tuviera lo haría pero con
but with respect I mean at the end of the
pero con respeto Es decir al final del
day it's not a debate it's an interview
día no es un debate es una entrevista
So I think they also have to
Entonces yo creo que también tienen que
understand that one thing is for me to come
entender que una cosa es que yo venga
here I can come here I can get involved
aquí yo puedo venir aquí me puedo mojar
here I tell you gu well Juan guarnizo what a
yo aquí te digo gu pues Juan guarnizo
loser and I can say it
vaya pringado y lo puedo decir
openly because it may be an
abiertamente porque puede ser una
opinion that I may or may not have but for
opinión que yo pueda tener o no pero por
example eh in the last podcast that I
ejemplo eh en el último podcast que he
recorded and that comes out now on Thursday which
grabado y que sale ahora el jueves que
is with Oli I don't give names of
es con Oli no doy nombres de
practically anyone because Oli is a
prácticamente nadie porque Oli es una
very reserved person who doesn't want
persona muy reservada que no quiere
problems I told him dude I can give
problemas yo le decía tío puedo meterle
[ __ ] to this guy because because I want to say
[__] a este porque porque quiero decir
this he told me no dude don't do
esto me decía él no cabrón no me hagas
this to me dude that I get along with that
esto tío que que yo me llevo con esa
person or I have and I say Okay well I'm not
persona o yo tengo y digo Okay pues no
going to give names and and the podcast  It's very
voy a dar nombres y y el podcast es muy
complete and it's very good but maybe
completo y está muy bien pero quizá la
people are going to miss a bit of
gente va a echar en falta un poco pues
the gossip that I can put in here because
el salseo que puedo meter aquí por qué
out of respect for the person that I have brought I'm
por respeto a la persona que he traído
not going to say certain things about third parties, well that's it.
no voy a decir ciertas cosas de terceros
If now, for example,
pues ya está si ahora por ejemplo viene
dasas comes and says, man,
dasas y me dice tío este tema en
don't touch this particular topic for me or
particular no me lo toques o me viene
Pepito comes and says,
Pepito y me dice este tema en particular
don't touch this particular topic for me because it's something very
no me lo toques porque es algo muy
personal and for whatever reason, well, I'm not going to
personal y por lo que sea pues no lo voy
touch it because I'm going to respect the
a tocar porque voy a respetar pues las
conditions of the imitated one. At the end of the day, there
condiciones del imitado al final del día
are also people there who believe
que también hay gente ahí que se cree
that I know that I cover everyone with
que yo que sé que yo unto a todos en
money, all the guests come for free,
dinero todos los invitados vienen gratis
so of course, when a guest comes, they
entonces claro cuando viene un invitado
come. In the end, they
vienen Al final a pasar un rato conmigo
monetize that content with me, they
ese contenido lo monetizó yo ellos
simply take whatever
simplemente se llevan pues la
repercussions they can get, so
repercusión que se puedan llevar
in the end, if they put
entonces yo al final Pues si me ponen
a series of deo on me, well, I fulfill it, you
una serie de de deo pues lo lo cumplo
know, and obviously I try to
sabes y obviamente trato de dar un buen
treat you well, I'll go more, eh. Although, for
trato te Ire más eh Aunque yo por
example, I may have given Cristal mly a
ejemplo a Cristal mly le haya metido un
bit of Caa today or I could have gotten
poco de Caña hoy o le haya podido meter
Juan Ari in, etc., if those people came
a Juan Ari etcétera si esa gente viniese
to the podcast That obviously there would be more
al podcast Que obviamente estarían más
than just guests I would do my role must be
que invitados yo haría mi rol debe ser
nice and be respectful and there would be
simpático y ser respetuoso y habría
people who would tell you you are not a hypocrite
gente que te diría no eres un hipócrita
and I say no Look you have that content I
y digo no Mira tú ties ese contenido
say You have that content or no I have to
digo Tú tieres ese contenido o no tengo
be professional I mean and also I would
que ser profesional es decir y además Yo
say to his face Look you are not a saint of
le diría a la cara Mira no eres santo de
my devotion Imagine that Juan comes I would
mi devoción Imagínate que viene Juan Yo
say to him Juan Look I don't like you but I'm
le diría Juan Mira no me caes bien pero
going to do my job well so I'm
voy a hacer bien mi trabajo así que te
going to treat you well and maybe
voy a dar un buen trato y a lo mejor
even The guy man after all I
incluso El chaval tío después de todo me
end up liking him less badly or even a
termina cayendo menos mal o incluso una
neutral reaction we don't know obviously
reacción neutral no se sabe obviamente
I understand that there are many people who would
yo entiendo que hay mucha gente que lo
see it as Ah What a hypocrite I don't know what I'm
vería como Ah Qué hipócrita no sé qué
saying it's not that man eh if you want a
digo no es que tío eh si tú quieres un
channel where both sides can come
canal en el que pueda venir tanto un
the Host has to be
lado como otro el el Host tiene que ser
as impartial as possible I mean if
lo más Imparcial posible o sea es que si
not nobody will come to the podcast you know it's that eh let's
no no va a venir nadie al podcast sabes
see clearly I understand that
es que é a ver claro Yo entiendo que a
what has bothered him is that you
él lo que le ha molestado es eso que tú
don't know how to refute but the thing is that in the end you
no sepas rebatir pero es que tú al final
are not as involved as I can be I
no estás tan metido como puedo estar yo
mean  If I have Ricky here
o sea si yo lo tengo aquí a Ricky
obviously I won't shut up It's fists
evidentemente yo no me callo Es punos
Of course but because you know it you know
Claro pero porque tú te lo sabes sabes
here is what I tell you I mean eh that
yo aquí es lo que te digo o sea eh que
you collaborate with Ricky or not having a
tú colabores con Ricky o no teniendo
relationship with him He can't tell you
relación con él Él no te puede decir
anything but it's that apart from one thing is that
nada pero es que aparte una cosa es que
you have a friend a friendship with
tú tengas un colega una mistad con
someone he can't tell you who
alguien no te puede decir con quién
to hang out with And who we won't go with I've
juntarte Y con quién no vamos yo te lo
told you here if he comes and and By He
he dicho a ti aquí si viene y y By Me
tells me he comes and goes I catch him here I
dice que viene y va Yo lo cojo aquí le
do an interview How the hell had I not
hago una entrevista Cómo [__] no le
caught an interview yb or gref you
había [__] una entrevista yb o a gref
understand anyway yes I tell you there are
me entiendes de todos modos sí te digo
people that for example you would
hay personas a las que por ejemplo no
never interview Eh yes it's true
entrevistarías nunca Eh sí que es verdad
that I have like a blacklist clo a
que yo tengo como una blacklist clo una
blacklist a blacklist if there is a Well I'm
blacklist una blacklist si hay un Bueno
not going to tell you the name here of any
no te voy a decir nombre aquí de alguno
but man I think it's understood
pero hombre Yo creo que se entiende
who I I I for the moment Look there is
quién yo yo yo por el momento Mira hay
one person that I would not bring for sure it is
una persona que no traería seguro que es
Comanche And look they have asked me And
Comanche Y mira que me lo han pedido Y
that but I am not going to bring him for reasons
eso pero no lo voy a traer por por temas
that I cannot talk about and then there is another that I would
que no puedo contar y luego hay otra que
have many doubts that is kku because
tendría muchas dudas que es kku porque
kcu would only bring him alone no no no I would only
kcu solo lo traería solo no no no solo
bring him if real on the condition
lo traería si real con la condición de
that he publicly admitted what he did and
que admitiera públicamente lo que hizo y
came with an intention of like no no
viniera con una intención de como no no
coming clean because it's impossible but yes
blanquearse porque es imposible pero sí
trying to say look I did this
tratar de decir mira yo he hecho esto
wrong I admit it like when you bring for
mal lo Admito como cuando traes por
example eh you know who Daniel Rojo is the
ejemplo eh sabes quién es Daniel rojo el
podcast he did with with Jordy w who was
podcast que hizo con con jordy w que era
a bank robber the guy doesn't go and
un atracador de bancos el tío no va y
says no I didn't rob he says Yes I did
dice no no he atracado dice Sí he
rob and that's what I did he says Look I
atracado y así lo hice dice Mira yo he
did this pum pum pum it could be even
hecho esto pum pum pum podría ser aún
so it would cost me because to this day I
así me me costaría porque a día de hoy
have him there in in the in many doubts
lo tengo ahí en en la en muchas dudas
because I see that he hasn't learned from his
porque veo que no ha no aprendido de sus
mistakes he is a person who is not
errores es una persona que no está
admitting what he has done and I think it would be
admitiendo lo que ha hecho y creo que
impossible not unthinkable but it would be
sería imposible no impensable pero sería
on the condition that he
con esa condición de que admita
openly admits look I screwed up done
abiertamente mira me he cagado hecho
this this this this and from there we
esto esto esto esto y de ahí ya se
could talk about the subject if not then
pudiera hablar sobre el tema si no pues
impossible and Comanche could not bring him
imposible y Comanche no lo podría traer
for issues eh For third party issues that
por temas eh Por temas de terceros que
no no but well in the end uh
no que no pero bueno que al final que eh
two things Dallas and it would be  Cool that it
dos cosas Dallas y sería Guay que
went up and you'll look good before it would be
subiera y quedaréis bien antes estaría
good before closing because in the end it
bien antes de que cerr porque al final
seems to me that it's nonsense I would have
me parece que una tontería Yo lo hubiera
said it privately that if it has
dicho por privado eso si si te ha
bothered you but more than anything because the
molestado pero más que nada porque la
ball eh you have done more it seems More
bola eh la habéis hecho más parece Más
than what and in the end they are two things that are
de lo que y al final son dos cosas que
spoken about I think it's nonsense I
se hablan Yo creo que es una tontería Yo
think it's nonsense the same look here
creo que es una tontería igual mira aquí
before at the beginning of the live you also
antes al principio del directo también
said something that was private that you
has dicho una cosa que era privada que
have messed up not with me because
has metido la pata no conmigo porque a
in that sense it does not affect me but
mí en ese sentido no me afecta pero
man you know but yes you know that it is the worst
hombre sabes pero s sabes que es lo peor
that you have screwed up Javi you Yes because you
que la has cagado tú Javi te Sí porque
have screwed up because I am going to
la has cagado tú porque yo lo te voy a
tell you I tell you what I am going to tell you
decir te digo lo que yo te voy a decir
about Auron It's that I simply
de auron Es que yo simplemente le
asked him man I'm going to say it now okay
pregunté tío lo voy a decir ahora vale
because you go you are going to realize that you have
porque vas te vas a dar cuenta de que le
given it importance Uy that
has dado importancia Uy que se me ha
the pun has dropped you have given it an importance
caído la pun le has dado una importancia
that Well then I pick it up that it did not have
que Bueno luego lo recojo que no tenía
because what I have said to How do you
porque yo lo que le he dicho a Cómo se
say to Auron was and man did you see this
dice a a auron fue e tío viste esta
miniature this I don't know what I don't know how many and
miniatura este no sé qué no sé cuántos y
he said yes yes already  I've already seen it
me dijo él sí sí ya lo he visto ya me
Javi told me he was going to upload that I don't know what I'm
dijo Javi que iba a subir eso no sé qué
saying to him [ __ ] Look at the guy, what a
le digo hostias Mira al cabrón vaya
title he put on you and he says yes the
título te ha puesto y me dice sí la
truth is that he puts some titles Like a little bit
verdad que pone unos títulos Así un poco
of Chernobyl a bit of a joke because
de chernóbil un poco la broma porque a
sometimes you put each title on me too
veces a mí también me pones cada título
at the slightest thing that I say anything
a la mínima que digo cualquier cosa Se
This and that is confirmed Oh God How
confirma esto y lo otro Ah Dios Qué
crazy I know that an attack has happened here
locura yo qu ha pasado un atentado aquí
in Hiroshima Now you know then without
en Hiroshima Ahora sabes entonces sin
more then I tell you that it was
más entonces ya te digo que era una
nonsense and that's it No what happens is that
tontería y ya está No lo que pasa es que
you have made it seem like whoever
tú has dejado entender como que quien te
confirmed it to you has been it has been it has been
lo ha confirmado ha sido ha sido es sido
your fault no no but let's see if you're
fallo tuyo no no pero a ver si le estás
telling him yes you're telling people
diciendo si le estás diciendo a la gente
that Auron knows leave it there already leave it there It is it is
que auron sabe déjalo ahí ya déjalo allá
but everyone but let's see
Es es pero todo el mundo pero a ver
guy Auron follows you on Instagram
cabrón auron te sigue en instagram todo
everyone knows that I see you but he doesn't
el mundo sabe que que te veo pero no me
tell me his private life listen to me No I did
cuenta su vida privada escúchame No yo
n't say that eh I didn't say that If
no dicho eso eh yo no he dicho eso Si
Dallas considers you a friend or something
Dallas te considera a ti un amigo o algo
more than a working relationship then he
más que una relación laboral a mí me
will continue to consider me his tilino I think
seguirá considerando su tilino yo creo
not because I don't even know  which is cool
que no porque no sé ni lo que es tilino
but when you sent him that gift for his
per cuando le mandaste el regalo ese por
birthday the one in the video said cool
el cumpleaños el del vídeo decía tilino
and he didn't understand it So I think it's
y él no lo entendía Así que yo creo que
missing context Dallas is very bad
que le falta contexto Dallas es muy mal
very bad eh bad there it's true bad there
muy mal eh mal ahí es verdad mal ahí
bad reaction there eh another audio t of TR
mala reacción ahí eh otro audio t de TR
minutes I put it block it vo I'm going to
minutos lo pongo lo bloqueo vo me voy a
hit myself I'm leaving guys I put it block it
pegar me voy chicos lo pongo lo bloqueo
listen to me I have I have what ivay told you
escúchame tengo tengo lo que te ha dicho
in his live tonight yeah
ivay en su directo de esta noche sí
[ __ ] good while you put it I'm going to
[__] buen mientras lo pones voy a
pick up something that I dropped
recoger una cosa que se me ha caído
while I put auda Ah okay very
mientras que pongo auda Ah vale muy
simple here we all work in the
sencillo aquí todos trabajamos de lo
same thing okay And there is no production company
mismo vale Y no hay ninguna productora
behind us what we have to
que nos diga detrás lo que tenemos que
do here none of us are
hacer aquí ninguno de nosotros somos
presenters of a program they give us
presentadores de un programa que nos den
a script and force us to do something
un guion y nos obliguen a hacer una cosa
for nothing each one has their own
para nada cada uno tiene su propio
program where they do and say how they want
programa donde hace y dice como quiere
when they want and in the way the
cuando quiere y y de la forma la que le
[ __ ] they want so for me as
da la [__] gana entonces para mí como
I am as a person I kill for a friend I don't care
soy yo como persona yo por un amigo mato
at all Okay then if
me da totalmente igual Vale entonces si
you eh or Javi or any person person
tú eh o Javi o cualquier persona person
just consider no no  for me
simplemente considera no no para mí las
friendships are on one side and for me what
amistades están a un lado y para mí lo
my programs say or what
que digan mis programas o lo que hagan
my programs do is on the other hand very
mis programas está por otro lado muy
well but then I don't don't ask me for
bien pero entonces yo no no me pidas
friendship Because for me friendship is
amistad Porque para mí la amistad está
above work and for me
por encima del trabajo y para mí por
above work there will always be
encima del trabajo siempre va a estar la
friendship and with which me
amistad y con lo cual el yo estar
gaining confidence with a person and
cogiendo confianza con una persona y que
that person not being able to be At the
esa persona no sea capaz de estar Al
same level as me is the same it's like
mismo nivel que yo es lo mismo es como
when you start a relationship with a
cuando tú inicias una relación con una
girl for example And you tell her you
chica por ejemplo Y tú le dices te
love me and the girl doesn't love you back
quiero y la chica no te devuelve te
obviously we don't have any
quiero obviamente no tenemos ninguna
relationship here whatsoever but
relación aquí ningún tipo pero se
the opadation is understood it makes no
entiende la opad ación no tiene ningún
[ __ ] sense that you ask me for friendship and that
[__] sentido que me pidas amistad y que
you behave as you please after
te comportes como te da la gana después
work for me those are two things that
del trabajo para mí son dos cosas que
are work below and friendship
está trabajo por debajo y la amistad por
above and if for you it is not We
encima y si para ti no lo está
simply cannot have that type
Sencillamente no podemos tener ese tipo
of friendship and that's it and we are just
de amistad y listo y somos sin más
colleagues obviously I do not stop liking you
colegas obviamente no me dejas de caer
or anything but we cannot be
bien ni mucho menos pero no podemos ser
friends That's simple Because for me
amigos Así es sencillo Porque para mí
before everything before videos
antes que todo antes que los vídeos
before work before
antes que el trabajo antes cualquier
anything for me there is loyalty loyalty
cosa para mí está la lealtad la lealtad
to my  friends and if there is no loyalty on
a mis amigos y si no hay lealtad por las
both sides for me no there can be no
dos partes para mí no no puede existir
friendship and that is the reason and I do not want to
una amistad y es la razón y no quiero
bring up shitty topics again here but it
sacar temas de [__] otra vez aquí pero
is the reason why I stopped being friends
es la razón por la que dejé de ser amigo
with Javi back in the day basically because I did not
de Javi en su día básicamente porque no
feel that there was the same that there was no
sentía que hubiese la misma que no
reciprocity basically between
hubiera reciprocidad básicamente entre
between me and that's how it is eh for him His
entre el yo y es así eh para él El su
work is above everything and he
trabajo está por encima de todo y él no
is not anyone's friend and he is going to criticize whoever he
es amigo de nadie y va a criticar qui le
needs when it is necessary for me
haga falta cuando le haga falta para mí
no for me no Simply And if
no para mí no Simplemente Y si el día de
tomorrow eh a friend of mine goes and makes the
mañana eh un amigo mío coge y hace la
world [ __ ] I am not going to be here
[__] del mundo yo no voy a estar aquí
releasing a [ __ ] video saying
sacando un [__] vídeo diciendo
nonsense from him the one I get
barbaridad des de él yo de quien saco
the [ __ ] [ __ ] from is the people with whom
las [__] [__] es de la gente con la
neither good nor bad I simply do not
que ni bien ni mal simplemente ni me
get along or I do not get along or I get along badly but
llevo o no me llevo o me llevo mal pero
with someone who is that I have been in
con alguien que está que yo he estado en
his house that We have played we have
su casa que Hemos jugado que hemos
spent nights playing that for me is not the
pasado noches jugando eso para mí no
same level and for me that always comes
está mismo nivel y para mí eso siempre
before work and that is how I
está por encima de trabajo y es como yo
see things and you have all the right
veo las cosas y tienes tod el derecho
in the world to see things differently than
del mundo a ver las cosas diferentes que
I  and everyone has the right
yo y tiene cualquier persona el derecho
to see things differently than
del mundo a ver las cosas diferentes a
I do but that's how I see
mí mismo pero yo así es como veo las
things and I can't be uh I can't
cosas y yo no puedo ser eh yo no puedo
have a level of friendship with someone
tener un nivel de amistad con alguien
who doesn't fight for me just like
que no se parte la cara por mí igual que
I fight for that person and that's it and that's it, that
yo me la parto por esa persona y ya está
's my point in
y punto ese ese ese es mi punto en
essence but is it my style or is it not my
esencia pero es mi tilino o no es mi
style I see him I see him hurt and I see him
tilino lo veo lo veo de doido y lo veo
hurt Uh I feel bad but today he's very
dolido Eh me sabe mal pero hoy está muy
sentimental uh I swear dasas we'll
sentimental eh yo te lo juro dasas ya
talk privately we'll talk
hablaremos por privado ya hablaremos por
privately but [ __ ] I mean it's left me
privado pero hostias o sea me ha dejado
broken I read a comment that
roto he leído un comentario que que me
almost made me cry when they
ha hecho casi se me qua la lagrimilla
say he lost a friend that he
que dicen delo ha perdido un amigo que
didn't even know he had uh I mean well let's
no sabía ni que tenía eh Es decir bueno
see I understand I understand I understand all the
a ver entiendo Entiendo entiendo todos
points but well I understand his
los puntos pero bueno Yo entiendo su
point and I understand his point But there's a
punto y entiendo su punto Pero hay un
big but I'm not that I'm criticizing
gran pero yo no es que esté criticando
I have not criticized daras for example
yo no he criticado a daras por ejemplo
in Rick's podcast at any time on the
en el podcast de Rick en ningún momento
contrary I defend him Ah there That
todo lo contrario lo defiendo Ah ahí Ahí
's where I would see That's where  I would see
es donde yo vería Ahí es donde yo vería
the subject clearly, me, me. This is the first thing,
el tema claro yo yo Esto es lo primero
I never in fact, eh, it has happened to me both
yo jamás de hecho Eh me ha pasado tanto
in favor of alas and against, Okay,
a favor de alas como en contra Vale
when daras has criticized, maybe in
cuando daras ha criticado A lo mejor en
his podcast he criticized in his day, eh, the millo
su podcast criticó en su día eh al millo
or he said, Well, to me, the millo, well this and that,
o dijo Pues a mí el millo pues esto y lo
or when the critical millo said, hey,
otro o cuando el millo crítico dije ey
careful, I mean, I always get involved
cuidado o sea es decir yo siempre me
in terms of if someone attacks in
mojo en cuanto a que si alguien ataca de
some way someone to whom I have a
alguna manera a alguien que yo tengo
good reaction, I say it, in fact, here
buena reacción yo lo digo de hecho aquí
many times they tell me that it's that telox,
muchas veces me dicen que es que telox
man, I don't know what and I say, I know that maybe you
tío no sé qué y digo yo sé que a lo
expect me to criticize
mejor esperáis que yo aquí critique a
someone here because it's like the enemy of the
alguien porque es como el enemigo de la
kids, but if that person has a
chavalería pero si esa persona tiene una
good relationship with me, I don't care.
buena relación conmigo me da igual
Even if the whole chat goes
Aunque todo el chat se me ponga en
against me, I'm going to keep saying what I
contra Yo voy a seguir diciendo lo que
think, so I think what
pienso entonces creo que lo que no ha
daras hasn't taken into account is that I also
tenido en cuenta daras es que yo también
have a good relationship with Ricky. So, that
tengo buena relación con Ricky Entonces
is to say, it's not that for me Ricky is a
es decir No es que para mí Ricky sea una
completely irrelevant person, I
persona completamente irrelevante yo a
don't consider Ricky a friend, he, I do
Ricky no lo considero un amigo él Creo
n't think I consider him a friend either. It's that
que tampoco me lo cons a mí Yo es que
for me, let's see, a friend  A friend can
para mí a ver un amigo Un amigo te puede
see you unless it's something that you
a ver a no ser que sea una cosa que le
're throwing [ __ ] at him to make him look bad and you
estés tirando [__] para dejarlo mal y
're throwing [ __ ] at him that's going to
le estés tirando [__] que le vaya a
hurt him. I think that a friend is also there
perjudicar Yo creo que un amigo también
to tell you the good and the bad
está para decirte lo bueno y lo malo
so that you understand me, I mean, me and I
para que tú me entiendas es decir yo y
don't want everything is bad eh but the relationship
no quiero todoes mal eh pero la relación
that I can have with Rick is similar to the one I
que puedo tener con Rick es parecía la
have with you, I get along well eh if
que tengo contigo me llevo bien eh si
tomorrow you ask me to meet up because you're coming
mañana me dices de quedar porque vienes
to Andorra I'm going to meet up with you I'm going to be
a andorra voy a quedar contigo voy a ser
super nice but damn I don't know
super simpático pero [__] No me sé toda
your whole life nor do I know his nor do I know myself
tu vida ni me sé la suya ni é se yo yo
in that sense, I mean eh yes I'm
en ese sentido o sea eh si yo me estoy
hanging out with Ricky And you, let's see, one thing is
Pando con Ricky Y tú a ver una cosa es
that you throw [ __ ] at me like something that
que me tires [__] en plan algo que me
could affect me something big you know something that
pueda afectar algo gordo sabes algo que
hurts me but if you have to be
me duela pero si tienes que estar en
against me in some things that I have done
contra mía en algunas cosas que yo haya
because it seems to you that I have done
hecho porque te parezca que lo he hecho
wrong Or something like that I know it would give me a little to
mal O tal yo que sé me daría un poco a
see I understand we also handle ourselves in
ver entiendo también nos manejamos en
this we are involved in controversial
esto estamos metidos en polémicas
discussions we make them mediatic
discusiones las hacemos mediáticas
So in that sense you know what I'm
Entonces en ese sentido sabes lo que te
telling you, I mean, in  that sense but well let's
digo o sea yo en ese sentido pero bueno
see if you talk for what
a ver si habláis por ha
you're giving it more importance that
conando le estáis dando más import eso
I think that yes that is that in the end
yo creo que sí que es eso que al final
more importance is given to what there is bad
se da más importancia la que hay mala
mine for what it touches me but as I tell you I
mía por lo que me toca pero ya te digo
think it has to have a
yo creo que tiene que tener un final
happy ending love has to come out Dalas I
feliz tiene que que salir el amor Dalas
love you okay That's it Sleep peacefully do
te quiero vale Ya está Duerme tranquilo
n't worry that it made me laugh
no te preocupes que me ha hecho gracia
that he said he said to me it's like if you tell your
que decía me decía es como si dices a tu
girlfriend I love you and she doesn't tell you and I was Like that I
novia quiero y no te lo dice y yo estaba
was
Así estaba
So calm I was sentimental
Así tranquil estaba sentimental
[Music]
[Música]
say
dí